I would become
a subject matter expert.
So let's say
for the context of this:
I've identified as
the Infofi team
I want Monad.
So I'm just gonna make
the most
cracked
Monad
threads
out the gate
for free
immediately.
I'm just gonna start
posting that shit
on the timeline
while I'm trynna
reach out to them.
In the context of this
framework
I'm a brilliant
educator.
So
Soo
Sooo
Soooo
my content is
going to stand out.
It's
quality > quantity
so people are
going to notice it.
And then
wen we're on the call:
they noticed me
from my content.
'Cause cold emails are
probably not gonna
go anywhere.
Most of it's gonna be from:
they've heard of me
from the timeline
'cause my threads are
CRACKED.
"Look guys:
I provided you
this content
for free,
BUT
a man's gotta eat."
I'm gonna provide
value first
but I wanna be paid
to create threads
for them.
And eventually
I want to build a product
THATHHAHTHT
again.
You kind of have to start
as a volunteer.
It sucks.
It feels
really
gross.
Because you know
the value you're bringing
should be paid.
But the issue is:
They don't.
but the issue is they don't
how good you are.
And they won't know
how good you are
until you've
proven yourself
You have to show them.
And be undeniable.